Yesterday I talked about a streamer who passed away while on stream, his name was Rafael Graven,
known online as Jean Parminov. He was a French streamer who was once a gamer, then started doing
more IRL content and teamed up with some real degenerates that mistreated him and abused him for
a very long time, and then they did a 10-day marathon with Jean Parminov where they strangled him,
beat him, humiliated him, some truly evil shit, and he unfortunately passed away while sleeping
on that stream. You can see all of this. It's very, very hard to watch. I looked into this super
deeply. Jean Parminov was an individual who went through a lot of struggle, and he was a vulnerable
person. And from what I can tell, this group with Naruto and Safanay, these are big French
streamers. They exploited his desire to be accepted by pretending to be his friend, and what they
wanted for Jean as their friend was to let them beat the fuck out of him and treat him like garbage,
dehumanize him, abuse him physically and mentally, and put him through torture on stream for their
content because it was very popular content. It was all broadcast on kick, and I speculated yesterday
that kick probably knew about it, turns out they 100% knew about it, and kick France would even make
tweets about Jean Parminov and the torture he was enduring. They were fully aware of what was
happening. They even used him to push their merch. So kick France, it's not like they can just
try and make the claim. This flew under our radar. If only we had known we would have swooped in,
like fucking Batman and saved Gotham City from this degeneracy. They knew they even were an
active participant in encouraging it clearly. So they can't just play like the blissful ignorance
card on it. Now from what I read, that kick Twitter account that was posting about it was run by
a French agency, so maybe like kick staff didn't particularly know, but I find that kind of hard
to believe that you would just let this agency have free reign and that never ever reports back to
kick itself. So I'm very confident they were aware of what was happening, but since these streams
were so popular, they were big. Like I knew they were very successful, but I didn't know how big
they were. These were huge streams, and since they were so huge, I think they were hesitant to
shut it down and given kick history of just letting illegal activity go unpunished for a really
long time, I think it's pretty safe to say that they saw the amount of eyeballs this was bringing
and they just let it ride. They didn't care that Jean Parmanov was literally being fucking abused
on their platform because it was getting some big time peepers on the platform. And I think
that needs to change ASAP for kick. This is a platform that's growing a lot and as I've said
this a lot, I think it's a good thing if kick continues to be successful competition. The streaming
space is crucial, but the way that they handle their own rules is laughable. It's just as bad as
the way Twitch handles their rules. Kick is not shutting down illegal activity on their platform,
and they need to. Again, I'm not saying had they shut down this marathon of abuse stream,
it would have saved Jean Parmanov's life, there's no way of knowing that. But at the very least,
you would have set the tone that abusing and fundamentally torturing a human being on your
platform is not welcome, which I think is a good stance to take. And it seems like it's something
that a lot of the streamers on kick would also like kick to step up and do. Again, I mentioned
this yesterday as another example. There is a streamer who is still actively streaming on kick.
As of me making this right now is literally live who has fucked multiple prostitutes on stream
and includes one time where he fucked a prostitute on stream with a child in the room while he
did it on stream. And that guy is still not banned. Kick needs to start actually taking crimes
seriously, which I can't believe is something that even needs to be said. But anyway, I'm not
going to rant about that any longer. The big update to today's story is a French investigation has
concluded that Jean Parmanov's death was not the result of any foul play. According to a
public prosecutor, there is a post-mortem conducted and he was found to have not been killed by trauma
or a third party. The probable causes of death appear to be medical and or toxicological.
This is from Damien Martinelli saying that further tests had been ordered. But ultimately,
they are concluding that this was not the result of all of the abuse and mistreatment that he
endured for so long from these streamers that were beating him and strangling him and torturing him.
Two forensic doctors found no internal or external traumatic injuries or burns, only a few bruises
and healed lesions. Medical experts considered that Mr. Graven's death was not traumatic in origin
and was not related to the intervention of a third party. Graven may have suffered from heart
problems and was undergoing medical treatment for his thyroid gland. There's a lot to unpack with
this. Now, while his actual cause of death might not be directly related to all of the beatings
and shit that he took from these fucking demons, I think it's inarguable that all of the stress
and all of the torture that he endured probably was pretty bad for his already present medical
conditions. I would make an argument now, of course, I'm not a medical expert, that
subjecting a human being with medical problems as well as a couple of other things going on in the
medical history to the amount of beatings, strangulation, stress, consumption of dangerous
chemicals, the sleep deprivation and doing your absolute best to ensure perpetual misery of that
individual probably exacerbates a lot of problems that could lead to their death. I would say
that is something that most sensible people would agree with. I think if someone has underlying
medical conditions, fundamentally torturing them is probably just going to make it worse. Even if
the torture doesn't directly kill them, I would be shocked if anyone thinks that this means that
those streamers hands are clean like up. Case closed. He didn't die from any of the trauma he
experienced. Yeah, he had some bruises and all that and yes, he was abused for so, so, so long
mistreated and fundamentally tortured by these individuals, but his actual death, well, it looks
like that was just of natural causes and had nothing to do with any of this innumerable amount of
torture that we've bore witness to. Surely that was all just circumstantial, had nothing to do with
any of that. They're blameless. These are just some, some saints here. These are angels actually.
These are just good friends of Raphael Graben who are clearly going to be mourning his loss
just as much as everyone else. They did nothing wrong. It was just, it was just medical problems that
in no way was impacted by the abuse that he was subjected to for such an extended period of time
from these individuals. I think all of the evidence that you can freely watch of all of the numerous
like unfathomable mountain of clips of them just beating the shit out of him and literally like
like abusing him constantly, fundamentally torturing this man would indicate that they definitely
played a role in making his overall health worse. And we have the text messages from Raphael Graben
to his mother that indicate how much stress he was under and how he felt like he was being held
hostage by them that he couldn't leave and that he desperately wanted out. It was so bad with their
abuse of this man that they actually had him on stream confirm that if he dies, it's not their fault.
I had to translate this, but in a clip that's out there, they are saying, well, what happens if
John Parmanov dies? They said, well, we're going to have to get him to say that it's not our fault
if he dies. It's a result of his lifelong bad health, his bad decisions, his terrible way of living
that led to his death if he dies. And he initially said, no, he didn't want to say that, but they
made him say that. They forced him to say that if he dies, it is not because of all of the abuse
that they subject him to. Does that sound like the actions of an innocent party here? They knew
that he was vulnerable. They knew that what they were doing could very well end up with him dead,
it seems. And then to try and cover their ass, they had him agree that if he dies, it's because
of his own health problems, which he initially declined to do, but they kept insisting that he
he clears them. Like, it's fucking absurd to try and make the claim that all of these streams,
the months worth of abuse, more than months, a long time of abuse they subjected John Parmanov to
had no role to play in his passing. It's craziness to try and make it seem like just because they
didn't like fucking kill him on the spot on stream that they had nothing to do with his death.
Now, something I've seen popping up from some real fucking brain dead morons here,
huffing stupid juice is that, well, he agreed to all of it so it's his fault, can't be mad at the
streamers. If that isn't the biggest load of fucking barnacles I've ever heard, first of all,
we know from the text messages, he didn't want to do it. He wanted to leave, but felt he couldn't
leave that he was being held hostage there. They weren't letting him leave. Was the impression he
was giving to a text message sent to his mother. Also, from what I was reading, they would actually
force him to do this sometimes monetarily. Like, they would financially pressure him to participate in
their abuse and mistreatment. And from the very good go, it feels like they manipulated a mentally
vulnerable, vulnerable man who was looking for friends into being their guinea pig to just beat
on stream for content to make money off of it. They treated this guy like a human piñata where they
would hit him until money fell out from like the deranged viewers that were watching and donating
and all of that. There is nothing here that indicates that he was a willing participant for everything.
Yes, he agreed to a certain level of extreme challenges, but clearly not all of it. Again,
we have the text messages that he sent to his mother. It's clear he didn't want to do all of it.
And it's clear on stream the amount of times he would say no to things, but they would still force
him to eventually just succumb to it and agree. Also, from what I was reading, I'm not super
familiar with the law in the region, but from what I read, you can't even legally consent to being
tortured or anything like that in the first place. So even if he fully agreed to everything,
it doesn't seem like you can legally even do that. You can't legally consent to fucking torture
on yourself. It's just this whole thing is indefensible in my eyes. Also, Naruto's a bitch.
This loser brings shame to the entire Hidden Leaf Village. He has ruined the Uzumaki name with this.
He has filed a cyberbullying complaint amid the backlash to all of this. He has the call to file
a cyberbullying complaint about his feelings being hurt with people insulting him for all of the abuse
that he subjected John Parmanov to. So he filed the complaint to the Paris Prosecutors Office
Cyber Hate Division targeting those who have harassed Naruto since JP's death. As he goes through
a period of mourning, Naruto is the subject of a cyberbullying campaign. These behaviors,
in addition to being immoral, constitute criminal offenses. A complaint will be filed in the coming
days with the Paris Prosecutors Office Cyber Hate Division so that the perpetrators can be identified
and prosecuted. You fucking vile worms. Imagine torturing a man for so long, so much mistreatment
and abuse broadcast on streams you can make money off of this man's misery. And now when that man
passes away, you are now trying to play the victim yourself like, oh, you guys are hurting our
feelings. How can you guys be mean to us? We've done nothing wrong. Those are best friends. Did you
not read our heartfelt post where we called him? Well, where Naruto called him his sidekick?
Did you also not read the part in Naruto's apology? That was so heartfelt where he said,
please stop sharing the final moments. Oh, man, what did you miss all of that? Because the final
moments make them look so bad because in the final moments he throws a fucking water bottle at JP's
lifeless body on the floor and then goes and slaps it to see if he'll be responsive only to find
out he's dead. Because for the entirety of that marathon stream, they're just abusing this poor guy.
What? Oh my god, did you miss all of that? It's so clear how much they love their best friend.
You guys are being mean to them. That's crazy. Oh my god. What does the world come to? We need to
identify and prosecute everyone who's left a nasty comment about Naruto and Safinay. It's so
fucking cringe. It's crazy. It is just craziness. This story has been so fucking gross and I can
only pray that they actually do face punishment here. Because now I'm starting to worry that they
won't. It looks like they might get away with it. I also learned that they'd actually been taken
in by French authorities earlier this year about everything they were putting John Parminov through
on stream, but they were released the same day. And then it ultimately leads to what happened here,
where they continue to do it because it looks like they're completely in the right legally over
there in France. I guess to continue mistreating this guy so they go continue to do it on stream and
it leads to a fucking tragedy with the passing of John Parminov at 46 years old. This shit is so evil.
Now again, all of this is happening in France, so a lot of the information that I get access to
is through translations. So it is a little hard to keep up with everything, like fully
accurately, but I'm doing the best I can. It is just so sad. Like this whole story of Raphael
Groven is just so sad, man. Like it breaks my heart to see this kind of shit. Anyway, I just wanted
to talk about it. See ya.